let myArray=[1,2,3,4];

const STORE=[
//question 1
{
    question: 'Approximately how many pounds of pumpkins are produced in the U.S. each year?',
    options: [
        '1.5 million pounds',
        '3 million pounds',
        '1.5 billion pounds',
        '3 billion pounds'
    ],
    answer: '1.5 billion pounds',
    additional: 'The U.S. grows 1.5 billion pounds of pumpkins per year. Roughly 1.3 billions pounds of that is grown in preparation for Halloween.',
},
//question 2
{
    question: 'Which Celtic Festival inspired Halloween?',
    options: [
        'Imbolc',
        'Samhain',
        'Beltane',
        'Litha'
    ],
    answer: 'Samhain',
    additional: 'During the ancient festival of Samhain, people celebrated the dead by offering treats outside of homes for wandering spirits to take.',
},
//question 3
{
    question: 'The first Jack O\'Lanterns were made from which vegetable?',
    options: [
        'Turnip',
        'Cabbage',
        'Cucumbers',
        'Broccoli'
    ],
    answer: 'Turnip',
    additional: 'The original Jack O\'Lanterns were carved out of turnips, as well as potatoes and beets.',
},
//question 4
{
    question: 'How many haunted houses are there in the U.S.?',
    options: [
        '1,200',
        '2,200',
        '3,200',
        '4,200'
    ],
    answer: '1,200',
    additional: 'There are estimated to be 1,200 haunted houses in the U.S. that charge admission.',
},
//question 5
{
    question: 'What is the most popular Halloween candy for the decade of the 2010\'s?',
    options: [
        'Candy Corn',
        'Twix',
        'Snickers',
        'Reese\'s Peanut Butter Cups'
    ],
    answer: 'Reese\'s Peanut Butter Cups',
    additional: '36% of Americans say that Reese\'s is their favorite Halloween candy. However, Skittles are the top-selling.',
},
//question 6
{
    question: 'Why is it considered bad luck for a black cat to cross your path?',
    options: [
        'They were believed to be witches.',
        'They may scratch, causing injury.',
        'Many poeple are allergic to cats.',
        'They could steal your Halloween candy.'
    ],
    answer: 'They were believed to be witches.',
    additional: 'Blame the pilgrims! The puritan pilgrims disapproved of witchcraft and many believed that witches could transform into black cats.',
},
//question 7
{
    question: 'What was Candy Corn originally called?',
    options: [
        'Tricolor Sugar',
        'Witch\'s Hat',
        'Chicken Feed',
        'Traffic Cones'
    ],
    answer: 'Chicken Feed',
    additional: 'Candy Corn was created in 1880 when roughly half of Americans lived on farms. Therefore, it was designed to look like chicken feed.',
},
//question 8
{
    question: 'Approximately how much money did Americans spend on Halloween in 2018?',
    options: [
        '$3 billion',
        '$5 billion',
        '$9 billion',
        '$12 billion'
    ],
    answer: '$5 billion',
    additional: 'That\'s a lot of money! Halloween is the second highest grossing commercial holiday after Christmas.',
},
//question 9
{
    question: 'How big was the largest pumpkin ever measured?',
    options: [
        '155 lbs',
        '389 lbs',
        '542 lbs',
        '836 lbs'
    ],
    answer: '836 lbs',
    additional: 'This huge pumpkin was grown by Norm Craven in 1993.',
},
//question 10
{
    question: 'Which U.S. city holds the biggest Halloween parade?',
    options: [
        'Chicago',
        'New York City',
        'Los Angeles',
        'Houston'
    ],
    answer: 'New York City',
    additional: 'More than two million people gather each year to view New York\'s Village Halloween Parade.',
}

]